Guide to the Stanford University Website Collection
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Schools, 2010-2011; Series 2
  - Medicine, 2010-2011
    - Surgery, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 14, surgery201109; 6.68 megabyte(s) (154 files in 49 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 7, surgery20120607; 466 megabyte(s) (152 files in 49 directories)
      - Abdominal Transplantation, Division of, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 6, transpl201110; 2.46 megabyte(s) (99 files in 27 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 6, transplantation20120806; 1.49 megabyte(s) (26 files in 11 directories)
      - Goodman Simulation Center, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 13, goodman201110; 5.16 megabyte(s) (146 files in 45 directories)
        - 2012 Dec 4, goodman20121204; 4.55 megabyte(s) (65 files in 15 directories)
      - Plastic and Reconstructive Surgery, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 6, plastic201110; 303 megabyte(s) (158 files in 47 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 6, plasticsurgery20120806; 588 megabyte(s) (78 files in 18 directories)
      - Vascular and Endovascular Surgery, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 6, vascular201110; 351 megabyte(s) (785 files in 98 directories)
        - 2012 Aug 6, vascular20120806; 247 megabyte(s) (643 files in 86 directories)
        - AAA STOP Program, 2011-2012
          - 2011 Oct 10, aaastop201110; 9.28 megabyte(s) (146 files in 41 directories)
          - 2012 Nov 6, aaastop20121106; 8.77 megabyte(s) (72 files in 21 directories)
    - Transplant Immunobiology Laboratory, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 12, til201110; 2.49 megabyte(s) (92 files in 16 directories)
      - 2012 Nov 29, til20121129; 2.45 megabyte(s) (87 files in 15 directories)
    - Urology, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 15, urology201109; 19.7 megabyte(s) (223 files in 36 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 27, urology20120627; 25.6 megabyte(s) (186 files in 34 directories)
    - Vera Moulton Wall Center, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 23, wall201110; 125 megabyte(s) (236 files in 33 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 29, wallcenter20120629; 90.8 megabyte(s) (222 files in 33 directories)
    - Women's Health, Program in, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 3, pwh201110; 37.6 megabyte(s) (185 files in 53 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 29, womenshealth20120629; 30.1 megabyte(s) (186 files in 54 directories)
- Centers and institutes, 2010-2012; Series 3
  - Advanced Molecular Photovoltaics, Center for, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 5, camp201110; 78.6 megabyte(s) (595 files in 13 directories)
    - 2012 Sep 19, camp20120919; 17 megabyte(s) (83 files in 8 directories)
  - Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, Center for, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Jan 4, casbs2011-032; 148 megabyte(s) (773 files in 86 directories)
    - 2012 Feb 9, casbs20120209; 26.4 megabyte(s) (764 files in 169 directories)
    - 2013 Feb 8, casbs20130208; 39.1 megabyte(s) (1121 files in 259 directories)
  - Aging Clinical Research Center, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Oct 25, aging201110; 58 megabyte(s) (357 files in 25 directories)
    - 2012 Apr 12, acrc20120412; 57.6 megabyte(s) (358 files in 29 directories)
    - 2013 Apr 8, acrc20130408; 30.7 megabyte(s) (350 files in 38 directories)
  - BiblioTech Program, 2013
    - 2013 Feb 15, bibliotech20130215; 92.3 megabyte(s) (6775 files in 48 directories)
  - Bill Lane Center for the American West, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Jul 1, west201107; 8.48 megabyte(s) (365 files in 92 directories)
    - 2012 April 12, west20120412; 169 megabyte(s) (990 files in 219 directories)
    - 2013 Apr 4, west20130404; 334 megabyte(s) (1664 files in 223 directories)
    - Water in the West, 2013
      - 2013 Apr 2, waterinthewest20130402; 63.3 megabyte(s) (290 files in 111 directories)
  - Bio-X, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Jan 4, biox2011-031; 189 megabyte(s) (1255 files in 129 directories)
    - 2012 Feb 9, biox20120209; 388 megabyte(s) (1370 files in 147 directories)
    - 2013 Feb 8, biox20130208; 318 megabyte(s) (1508 files in 201 directories)
  - Biodesign Program, 2011
    - 2011 Jul 6, biod201107; 329 megabyte(s) (1525 files in 95 directories)
  - Brown Institute for Media Innovation, 2012
    - 2012 Jul 24, brown20120724; 9.57 megabyte(s) (134 files in 11 directories)
  - Cargenie Institute for Science, Department of Plant Biology, 2011
    - 2011 Aug 15, dpb201108; 7.67 megabyte(s) (198 files in 46 directories)
  - Clean Slate Interdisciplinary Research Center, 2011-2012
    The Clean Slate Interdisciplinary Research Program was discontinued in January 2012.
    - 2011 Oct 5, cleanslate201110; 85.8 megabyte(s)
    - 2012 Sep 24, cleanslate20120920; 1.5 megabyte(s) (100 files in 14 directories)
  - Collaborative Haptics and Robotics in Medicine Lab, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 5, charm201110; 9.91 megabyte(s) (139 files in 9 directories)
    - 2012 Sep 20, charm20120920; 64 megabyte(s) (114 files in 37 directories)
  - Collaboratory for Research on Global Projects, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 5, crgp201110; 890 megabyte(s) (4,324 files in 234 directories)
    - 2012 Sep 20, crgp20120920; 561 megabyte(s) (4421 files in 241 directories)
  - Comparative Studies in Race and Ethnicity, Center for, 2011-2012
    - 2011 May 17, 354 megabyte(s) (10,198 files in 82 directories)
    - 2012 Mar 9, ccrse20120309; 949 megabyte(s) (24,707 files in 89 directories)
  - Compassion and Altruism Research and Education, Center for, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 11, ccare201110; 153 megabyte(s) (6504 files in 127 directories)
    - 2012 Nov 28, ccare20121128; 165 megabyte(s) (6,677 files in 114 directories)
  - Computer Assisted Research in the Humanities, Center for, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jul 12, ccarh201107; 584 megabyte(s) (5673 files in 582 directories)
    - 2012 Apr 19, ccarh20120419; 374 megabyte(s) (5090 files in 511 directories)
  - Confucius Institute, 2011
    For post-2011 captures, see School of Humanities and Sciences, Division of East Asian Languages and Culture.
    - 2011 May 17, conf_2011-125; 1.56 megabyte(s) (51 files in 11 directories)
  - Design, Institute of, at Stanford, 2010-2013
    - 2010 Dec 16, dschool2011-020; 5509.12 megabyte(s) (10,822 files in 7908 directories)
    - 2012 Feb 10, dschool20120210; 13721.6 megabyte(s) (28,828 files in 11,546 directories)
    - 2013 Feb 14, dschool20130214; 3267 megabyte(s) (29,745 files in 12,349 directories)
    - Design Program, 2012
      - 2012 Aug 29, designprogram20120829; 8.85 megabyte(s) (160 files in 6 directories)
      - @Stanford, 2013 Nov 5; 10.2 megabyte(s) (117 files in 115 directories)
        Redesigning the Stanford experience for 2020.
  - Education Policy Analysis, Center for, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jul 21, cepa201107; 301 megabyte(s) (3651 files in 87 directories)
    - 2012 Apr 20, cepa20120420; 934 megabyte(s) (18,985 files in 146 directories)
  - Education Program for Gifted Youth, 2012
    - 2012 Jul 31, epgy20120731; 237 megabyte(s) (1946 files in 188 directories)
  - Energy and Environment Affiliates Program, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 10, eeap201110; 8.13 megabyte(s) (161 files in 34 directories)
    - 2012 Sep 24, eeap20120924; 9.76 megabyte(s) (151 files in 45 directories)
  - Energy Modeling Forum, 2011
    - 2011 Jul 21-22, emf201107; 1157.12 megabyte(s) (1069 files in 783 directories)
    - 2012 Apr 26, emf20120426; 1699.8 megabyte(s) (1173 files in 820 directories)
  - Ford Doresey Program in International Policy Studies, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Sep 15, ips201109; 46.9 megabyte(s) (325 files in 43 directories)
    - 2012 Jun 11, ips20120611; 40.7 megabyte(s) (196 files in 38 directories)
  - Freeman Spogli Institute for International Studies (FSI), 2012
    - 2012 Feb 13, fsi20120213; 1382.4 megabyte(s) (49314 files in 53516 directories)
    - Walter H. Shorenstein Asia-Pacific Research Center, 2012
      - 2012 April 16, aparc20120416; 86.5 megabyte(s) (4609 files in 3176 directories)
      - Asian Health Policy Program, 2012
        - 2012 Apr 23, asiahealth20120423; 800 megabyte(s) (33,494 files in 32,159 directories)
      - Corporate Affiliates Program, 2012
        - 2012 Apr 25, aparcfellows20120425; 772 megabyte(s) (33,009 files in 31,736 directories)
      - Japan Studies Program, 2012
        - 2012 Apr 23, jsp20120423; 765 megabyte(s) (32,279 files in 31,148 directories)
      - Korean Studies Program, 2012
        - 2012 Apr 24, ksp20120424; 908 megabyte(s) (38,031 files in 36,594 directories)
      - Southeast Asia Forum, 2012
        - 2012 Apr 24, seaf20120424; 858 megabyte(s) (36,998 files in 35,883 directories)
      - Stanford China Program, 2012
        - 2012 Apr 25, china20120425; 795 megabyte(s) (33,262 files in 32,152 directories)
    - Center on Democracy, Development, and the Rule of Law, 2012; cddrl20120614; 1843.2 megabyte(s) (948,605 files in 47,035 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 14, cddrl20120614
      - Program on Arab Reform and Democracy, 2012
        - 2012 Jul 5, arabreform20120705; 836 megabyte(s) (33,407 files in 23,226 directories)
      - Governance Project, 2012
      - Human Rights Project, 2012
      - Liberation Technology, 2012
      - Program on Policy and Governance, 2012
      - Program on Social Entrepreneurship, 2012
    - Center for International Security and Cooperation, 2012
      - 2012 May 7, cisac20120507
    - Center on Food Security and the Environment, 2011-2012
      - 2012 Jun 25, foodsec20120625; 1208.32 megabyte(s) (37,664 files in 36,326 directories)
      - 2011 Oct 18, foodsec201110; 967 megabyte(s) (30,588 files in 30,225 directories)
    - Rural Education Action Project
    - Center for Health Policy / Center for Primary Care and Outcomes Research, 2012
      - 2012 May 1, healthpolicy20120501; 905 megabyte(s) (29,628 files in 30,004 directories)
    - The Europe Center, 2012
      - 2012 Jun 15, europe20120615; 1239 megabyte(s) (42,452 files in 41,121 directories)
    - Program on Energy and Sustainable Development, 2012
      - 2012 Jun 18, pesd20120618; 1280 megabyte(s) (44,543 files in 42,438 directories)
  - Fuelcell Research, 2012
    - 2012 Jul 25, fuelcell20120725; 0.53 megabyte(s) (27 files in 8 directories)
  - Geballe Laboratory for Advanced Materials (GLAM), 2011-2013
    - 2011 Jan 11, 5.77 megabyte(s) (68 files in 8 directories)
    - 2012 Feb 10, glam20120210; 11.2 megabyte(s) (69 files in 8 directories)
    - 2013 Feb 4, glam20130204; 11.2 megabyte(s) (66 files in 9 directories)
  - Ginzton Lab, 2010-2013
    - 2010 Dec 16, ginzton2011-019; 8.55 megabyte(s) (107 files in 18 directories)
    - 2012 Feb 10, ginzton20120210; 15.3 megabyte(s) (108 files in 18 directories)
    - 2013 Feb 4, ginzton20130204; 15.6 megabyte(s) (93 files in 18 directories)
  - Photonics Research Center, 2012
    - 2012 Nov 12, photonics20121112; 10.6 megabyte(s) (480 files in 52 directories)
  - Global Climate and Energy Project, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 10-11, gcep201110; 3840 megabyte(s) (2334 files in 172 directories)
    - 2012 Oct 1, gcep20121001; (2803 files in 204 directories)
  - Gravity Probe B, 2011
    - 2011 Jul 25-27, eins201107; 5569.32 megabyte(s) (6566 files in 178 directories)
  - Hansen Experimental Physics Lab (HEPL), 2011-2013
    - 2011 Jan 11, hepl2011-041; 33.1 megabyte(s) (242 files in 18 directories)
    - 2012 Feb 10, hepl20120210; 199 megabyte(s) (284 files in 18 directories)
    - 2013 Feb 4, hepl20130204; 62.5 megabyte(s) (263 files in 18 directories)
  - History Education Group, 2012
    - 2012 Jul 24, sheg20120724; 103 megabyte(s) (319 files in 44 directories)
    - Beyond the Bubble, 2012
      - 2012 Nov 15, beyondthebubble20121115; 55.7 megabyte(s) (671 files in 82 directories)
    - Teaching with Primary Sources, 2012
      - 2012 Nov 15, tps20121115; 0.42 megabyte(s) (43 files in 10 directories)
  - History and Philosophy of Science, Center for the, 2012
    - 2012 Jul 26, cisst20120726; 9.98 megabyte(s) (62 files in 4 directories)
  - Hoover Institution, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jan 12, hoover2011-047; 1484.8 megabyte(s) (19,022 files in 804 directories)
    - 2012 Feb 10, hoover20120210; 6103.04 megabyte(s) (59,686 files in 1400 directories)
    - 2013 Feb 20, hoover20130220; 2273.28 megabyte(s) (28,011 files in 967 directories)
  - Hopkins Marine Station, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Jul 29, hms201107; 137 megabyte(s) (766 files in 19 directories)
    - 2012 May 2, marine20120502; 323 megabyte(s) (1104 files in 31 directories)
    - 2013 May 1, marine20130501; 308 megabyte(s) (1252 files in 32 directories)
  - Human Sciences and Technologies Advanced Research Institute (H-STAR), 2010-2013
    - 2010 Dec 17, hstar2011-027; 9.38 megabyte(s) (128 files in 7 directories)
    - 2012 Feb 9, hstar20120209; 14.3 megabyte(s) (188 files in 37 directories)
    - 2013 Feb 4, hstar20130204; 28.4 megabyte(s) (203 files in 34 directories)
    - MediaX, 2012-2013
      - 2012 May 3, mediax20120503; 224 megabyte(s) (222 files in 34 directories)
      - 2013 May 1, mediax20130501; 4.04 megabyte(s) (52 files in 9 directories)
    - Stanford Persuasive Tech Lab, 2012
      - 2012 Jul 24, captology20120724; 7.29 megabyte(s) (179 files in 43 directories)
  - Innovation in Global Health, Center for, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 17, globalhealth201110; 295 megabyte(s) (588 files in 171 directories)
    - 2012 Dec 5, globalhealth20121205; 193 megabyte(s) (643 files in 184 directories)
  - Integrated Facility Engineering, Center for, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Aug 2, cife201108; 1730.56 megabyte(s) (2973 files in 193 directories)
    - 2012 May 3, cife20120503; 1423.36 megabyte(s) (2644 files in 189 directories)
    - 2013 May 1, cife20130501; 1576.96 megabyte(s) (12,495 files in 41 directories)
    - e-AEC Research, 2012
      - 2012 Jul 24, eaec20120724; 40.9 megabyte(s) (103 files in 15 directories)
  - Interfacial Engineering in Microelectromechanical Systems, Center on, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 5, ciems201110; 27 megabyte(s) (34 files in 6 directories)
    - 2012 Nov 12, ciems20121112; 27.3 megabyte(s) (34 files in 6 directories)
  - Inter-University Center for Japanese Language Study, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Sep 15, ius201109; 40.6 megabyte(s) (67 files in 5 directories)
    - 2012 Jun 12, iuc20120612; 59.1 megabyte(s) (70 files in 5 directories)
    - 2013 May 20, iuc20130520; 55.7 megabyte(s) (90 files in 5 directories)
  - Iris and B. Gerald Cantor Center for Visual Arts, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Jan 6, 149 megabyte(s) (1820 files in 104 directories)
    - 2012 Feb 8, cantor20120208; 347 megabyte(s) (1961 files in 113 directories)
    - 2013 Feb 8, 100 megabyte(s) (1279 files in 111 directories)
  - Jasper Ridge Biological Preserve, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Aug 3, jrbp201108; 34.5 megabyte(s) (753 files in 75 directories)
    - 2012 May 8, jrbp20120508; 207 megabyte(s) (881 files in 97 directories)
    - 2013 May 3, jrbp20130503; 196 megabyte(s) (1,080 files in 121 directories)
  - John W. Gardner Center for Youth and Their Communities, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 4, gardner201110; 80 megabyte(s) (248 files in 13 directories)
    - 2012 Sep 18, gardner20120918; 120 megabyte(s) (299 files in 43 directories)
  - John S. Knight Journalism Fellowships at Stanford, 2012
    - 2012 Jul 30, knight20120730; 112 megabyte(s) (1406 files in 542 directories)
  - Kavli Institute for Particle Astrophysics and Cosmology (KIPAC), 2010-2013
    - 2010 Dec 16, kipac2011-023; 244 megabyte(s) (657 files in 32 directories)
    - 2012 Feb 10, kipac20120210; 456 megabyte(s) (654 files in 32 directories)
    - 2013 Feb 4, kipac20130204; 223 megabyte(s) (842 files in 142 directories)
  - Language Center, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Aug 3, langcenter201108; 29.4 megabyte(s) (428 files in 48 directories)
    - 2012 May 8, language20120508; 34.2 megabyte(s) (388 files in 49 directories)
    - 2013 Feb 19, language20130219; 228 megabyte(s) (1471 files in 153 directories)
  - Logic at Stanford, 2012
    - 2012 Jul 30, logic20120730; 163 megabyte(s) (175 files in 15 directories)
  - Longevity, Center on, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Jan 11, long2011-045; 250 megabyte(s) (1333 files in 420 directories)
    - 2012 Feb 9, longevity20120209; 814 megabyte(s) (3514 files in 2317 directories)
    - 2013 Feb 4, longevity20130204; 471 megabyte(s) (3853 files in 2918 directories)
  - Magnetic Nanotechnology, Center for, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 5, nanomag201110; 13.7 megabyte(s) (72 files in 13 directories)
    - 2012 Sep 19, nanomag20120919; 12.4 megabyte(s) (61 files in 11 directories)
  - Master of Liberal Arts Program, 2012
    - 2012 Jul 9, mla20120709; 6.12 megabyte(s) (149 files in 23 directories)
  - Mathematics Research Center, 2011-2012
    - 2011 May 17, mrc_2011-126; 4.71 megabyte(s) (110 files in 19 directories)
    - 2012 March 9, mrc20120309; 4.7 megabyte(s) (110 files in 19 directories)
  - Medieval and Early Modern Studies, Center for, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Aug 8, mems201108; 8.23 megabyte(s) (61 files in 20 directories)
    - 2012 May 10, cmems20120510; 629 megabyte(s) (3253 files in 335 directories)
    - 2013 May 3, cmems20130503; 715 megabyte(s) (5566 files in 452 directories)
  - Michelle R. Clayman Institute for Gender Research, 2011-2013
    - 2011 May 17, 323 megabyte(s) 2879 files in 1588 directories)
    - 2012 March 9, clayman20120309; 596 megabyte(s) (6608 files in 1707 directories)
    - 2013 Mar 6, gender20130306; 315 megabyte(s) (4066 files in 255 directories)
  - Mobile and Social Computing Research Group, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 13, mobi201110; 176 megabyte(s) (476 files in 262 directories)
    - 2012 Oct 4, mobisocial20121004; 205 megabyte(s) (1016 files in 314 directories)
  - Morrison Institute for Population and Resource Studies, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Aug 10, morr201108; 291 megabyte(s) (259 files in 117 directories)
    - 2012 May 17, morrison20120517; 2.55 megabyte(s) (157 files in 130 directories)
    - 2013 May 3, morrison20130503; 295 megabyte(s) (325 files in 137 directories)
  - Nanoscale Materials and Processes, Initiative for, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 12, inmp201110; 591 megabyte(s) (198 files in 42 directories)
    - 2012 Oct 3, inmp20121003; 0.6 megabyte(s) (72 files in 44 directories)
  - Nanoscale Prototyping Laboratory, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Aug 12, npl201108; 165 megabyte(s) (476 files in 25 directories)
    - 2012 May 21, npl20120521; 113 megabyte(s) (481 files in 22 directories)
    - 2013 May 6, npl20130506; 135 megabyte(s) (491 files in 22 directories)
  - Nanostructuring for Efficient Energy Conversion, Center on, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 5, cneec201110; 83.5 megabyte(s) (891 files in 85 directories)
    - 2012 Sep 20, cneec20120920; 5.2 megabyte(s) (144 files in 39 directories)
  - National Board Resource Center at Stanford University, 2011
    - 2011 Oct 4, nbrc201110; 15.9 megabyte(s) (173 files in 45 directories)
    - 2012 Sep 18, nbrc20120918; 4.06 megabyte(s) (90 files in 51 directories)
  - National Consortium for Multicultural Education for Health Professionals, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 14, culturalmed201110; 14.6 megabyte(s) (208 files in 37 directories)
    - 2012 Dec 5, culturalmeded20121205; 14.4 megabyte(s) (169 files in 34 directories)
  - Neuromuscular Biomechanics Lab, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 14, nmbl201110; 326 megabyte(s) (467 files in 46 directories)
    - 2012 Oct 4, nmbl20121004; 186 megabyte(s) (496 files in 47 directories)
  - NIH Center for Biomedical Computation at Stanford, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 20-23, symbios201110; 7116.8 megabyte(s) (506 files in 89 directories)
    - 2012 Oct 11, simbios20121011; 5683 megabyte(s) (403 files in 87 directories)
  - Non-Volatile Memory Technology Initiative, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 14, nmtri201110; 166 megabyte(s) (63 files in 30 directories)
    - 2012 Oct 5, nvmti2012105; 167 megabyte(s) (92 files in 25 directories)
  - Ocean Solutions, Center for, 2011
    - 2011 Aug 12, cos201108; 998 megabyte(s) (5464 files in 9724 directories)
  - Opportunity Policy in Education, Center for, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Aug 31, 217 megabyte(s) (935 files in 117 directories)
    - 2012 May 22, edpolicy20120522; 319 megabyte(s) (1,187 files in 127 directories)
    - 2013 May 7
  - Pervasive Parallelism Lab, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 14, ppl201110; 86.1 megabyte(s) (267 files in 93 directories)
    - 2012 Oct 5, ppl20121005; 95.3 megabyte(s) (138 files in 34 directories)
  - Philanthropy and Civil Society, Center on, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Aug 15, pacs201108; 7.31 megabyte(s) (250 files in 50 directories)
    - 2012 May 21, pacs20120521; 140 megabyte(s) (313 files in 63 directories)
    - 2013 May 6, pacscenter20130506; 156 megabyte(s) (291 files in 66 directories)
  - Polymer Interfaces and Macromolecular Assemblies, Center on, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Aug 30, cpima201108; 41.5 megabyte(s) (1055 files in 711 directories)
    - 2012 May 22, cpima20120522; 48.4 megabyte(s) (821 files in 680 directories)
    - 2013 May 7, cpima20130507; 24.7 megabyte(s) (754 files in 698 directories)
  - Position, Navigation and Time, Center for, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Aug 30, scpnt201108; 643 megabyte(s) (197 files in 20 directories)
    - 2012 May 22, scpnt20120522; 461 megabyte(s) (220 files in 22 directories)
    - 2013 May 7, scpnt20130507; 289 megabyte(s) (235 files in 24 directories)
  - Poverty and Inequality, Stanford Center on, 2012
    - 2012 Jul 23, scspi20120723; 265 megabyte(s) (614 files in 72 directories)
  - Precourt Energy Efficiency Center, 2012
    - 2012 Aug 28, peec20120828; 17.1 megabyte(s) (313 files in 78 directories)
  - Precourt Institute for Energy, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Jan 4, pie2011-043; 2560 megabyte(s) (4764 files in 1343 directories)
    - 2012 Feb 9, pie20120209; 179 megabyte(s) (165 files in 18 directories)
    - 2013 Feb 4, energy20130204; 1096 megabyte(s) (3952 files in 135 directories)
  - Predictive Science Academic Alliance Program, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 14, psaap201110; 53.8 megabyte(s)
    - 2012 Oct 5, psaap20121005; 31.4 megabyte(s) (314 files in 26 directories)
  - Programmable Open Mobile Internet, 2012
    - 2012 Nov 12, pomi20121112; 137 megabyte(s) (126 files in 54 directories)
  - Project-Based Learning Lab, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Oct 17, pbl201110; 284 megabyte(s) (738 files in 150 directories)
    - 2012 Oct 8, pbl20121008; 278 megabyte(s) (736 files in 162 directories)
  - PULSE Institute for Ultrafast Energy Science, 2010-2013
    - 2010 Dec 16, pulse2011-022; 20.4 megabyte(s) (266 files in 16 directories)
    - 2012 Feb 10, pulse20120210; 37.2 megabyte(s) (228 files in 19 directories)
    - 2013 Feb 4, pulse20130204; 30.2 megabyte(s) (229 files in 17 directories)
  - Research in the Social Sciences, Institute for, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Aug 31, 325 megabyte(s) (675 files in 105 directories)
    - 2012 May 23, iriss20120523; 453 megabyte(s) (689 files in 114 directories)
    - 2013 May 7, iriss20130507; 883 megabyte(s) (703 files in 105 directories)
  - Research on Education Outcomes, Center for, 2012
    - 2012 Jul 25, credo20120725; 44.7 megabyte(s) (98 files in 8 directories)
  - Research on Education Policy and Practice, Institute for, 2011
    - 2011 Oct 4, irepp201110; 260 megabyte(s) (824 files in 120 directories)
  - Revs Program at Stanford
    - 2012 Jul 9, revs20120709; 10.4 megabyte(s) (66 files in 35 directories)
  - Solar Car Project, 2012
    - 2012 Sep 24, solarcar20120924; 6.92 megabyte(s) (75 files in 158 directories)
  - Solar Center, 2012
    - 2012 Sep 26, solarcenter20120926; 3737.6 megabyte(s) (3369 files in 339 directories)
  - Spectrum (Stanford Center for Clinical and Translation Education and Research), 2011-2013
    - 2011 Jan 4, spectrum2011-030; 6.12 megabyte(s) (281 files in 75 directories)
    - 2012 Aug 1, spectrum20120801; 9.82 megabyte(s) (91 files in 24 directories)
    - 2013 Feb 8, 23.8 megabyte(s) (652 files in 23 directories)
  - Stanford Center at Peking University, 2012
    - 2012 Apr 24, scpku20120424; 4.81 megabyte(s) (121 Files in 23 directories)
  - Stanford Center for Legal Informatics, 2011
    - 2011 Oct 4, codex201110; 3.56 megabyte(s) (21 files in 5 directories)